[{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980408909,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":21550,"timeElapsed":240114},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980410358,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":1448,"timeElapsed":241563},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980411629,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1269,"timeElapsed":242834},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980412927,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1297,"timeElapsed":244132},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980413935,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":1007,"timeElapsed":245140},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980414879,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":942,"timeElapsed":246084},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980415845,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":965,"timeElapsed":247049},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980417835,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1989,"timeElapsed":249040},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980419739,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":1903,"timeElapsed":250944},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980422057,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":1614,"timeElapsed":253262},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980423055,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":997,"timeElapsed":254260},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980423638,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":582,"timeElapsed":254843},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980425193,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":1554,"timeElapsed":256398},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980426143,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":949,"timeElapsed":257348},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980426969,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":826,"timeElapsed":258174},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980427538,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":568,"timeElapsed":258743},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980428503,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":964,"timeElapsed":259708},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980432664,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":4160,"timeElapsed":263869},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980433953,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":1288,"timeElapsed":265158},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980436099,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":1485,"timeElapsed":267304},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980437934,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1835,"timeElapsed":269139},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980441126,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3191,"timeElapsed":272331},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980442210,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":1084,"timeElapsed":273415},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980443328,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":1118,"timeElapsed":274533},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980444366,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1037,"timeElapsed":275571},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980445524,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":1157,"timeElapsed":276729},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980446494,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":969,"timeElapsed":277699},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980447630,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"114","question":"What are your personal life or career priorities?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1135,"timeElapsed":278835},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980660378,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":3130,"timeElapsed":491583},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980661537,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1158,"timeElapsed":492742},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980662615,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":1077,"timeElapsed":493820},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980663587,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":971,"timeElapsed":494792},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980664687,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1100,"timeElapsed":495892},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980665743,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":1055,"timeElapsed":496948},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980666718,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":974,"timeElapsed":497923},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980670160,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3441,"timeElapsed":501365},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980671646,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":1485,"timeElapsed":502851},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980674271,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1843,"timeElapsed":505476},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980678154,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":3882,"timeElapsed":509359},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980679729,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":1574,"timeElapsed":510934},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980681285,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1555,"timeElapsed":512490},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980682411,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":1126,"timeElapsed":513616},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980684165,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":1753,"timeElapsed":515370},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980685165,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":999,"timeElapsed":516370},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980686263,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":1097,"timeElapsed":517468},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980688503,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2239,"timeElapsed":519707},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980690506,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2002,"timeElapsed":521711},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982281770,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":1590560,"timeElapsed":2112975},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982282458,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":687,"timeElapsed":2113663},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982283235,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":776,"timeElapsed":2114440},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982284190,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":953,"timeElapsed":2115395},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982286299,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2109,"timeElapsed":2117504},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982287262,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":962,"timeElapsed":2118467},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982288077,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":814,"timeElapsed":2119282},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982288994,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":916,"timeElapsed":2120199},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982291428,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":2433,"timeElapsed":2122633},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982294011,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":1898,"timeElapsed":2125216},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982294824,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":812,"timeElapsed":2126029},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982295481,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":656,"timeElapsed":2126686},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982296102,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":620,"timeElapsed":2127307},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982296749,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":647,"timeElapsed":2127954},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982298016,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":1266,"timeElapsed":2129221},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982298858,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":841,"timeElapsed":2130062},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982300475,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1616,"timeElapsed":2131680},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982303271,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":2795,"timeElapsed":2134476},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982305311,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1366,"timeElapsed":2136516},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982306049,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":737,"timeElapsed":2137254},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982306930,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":880,"timeElapsed":2138135},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982307642,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":712,"timeElapsed":2138847},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982308361,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":717,"timeElapsed":2139566},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982309455,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1093,"timeElapsed":2140660},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982310358,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":903,"timeElapsed":2141563},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982311140,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":781,"timeElapsed":2142345},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982313332,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2191,"timeElapsed":2144537},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982315063,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":1063,"timeElapsed":2146268},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982316026,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":963,"timeElapsed":2147231},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982316979,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":952,"timeElapsed":2148184},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982317948,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":968,"timeElapsed":2149153},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982319037,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1088,"timeElapsed":2150241},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982320526,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1489,"timeElapsed":2151731},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982321551,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1023,"timeElapsed":2152756},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982322675,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":1123,"timeElapsed":2153880},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982323771,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1096,"timeElapsed":2154976},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982326471,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2021,"timeElapsed":2157676},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982327204,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":732,"timeElapsed":2158409},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982327974,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":770,"timeElapsed":2159179},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982328837,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":862,"timeElapsed":2160042},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982329769,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":931,"timeElapsed":2160974},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982330662,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":893,"timeElapsed":2161867},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982331707,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":1044,"timeElapsed":2162912},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982332622,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":913,"timeElapsed":2163827},{"subjectID":"vzu8jjlvo1","prolificID":"5765c0fcf2e23200017ded5e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23f6d74e3f22c5fc133","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982333610,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":987,"timeElapsed":2164815}]